We're going to do gathering chi from heaven and earth.
And I want you to, if you'd like to follow along with me, that'd be great.
But gathering chi from heaven and earth, one of the great things about Qigung is that the movements can be very, very simple.
We don't have to do any complex movements here.
There are complex movements later on in higher levels of Qigung.
But the wonderful thing about Qigung is that Quigung can be done with any age group.
Any age group.
We have movements in Qigung that eighty year olds can do, ninety year olds can do.
We have movements in Quigung that require stronger flexibility, more endurance and so on.
But the point to this is that when you do Qigung, you can do so many different movements.
There are so many movements in Qigung that, when you learn a great amount of Qigung, you could pick what you would like to do, what your body can handle.
OK?
And, a real simple one is gathering chi from heaven and earth.
And what I'd like to do is demonstrate the form for you and kind of just talk through the form as you're watching me do this.
So, we always want to start out in the Wu Chi posture.
Right -- first one, always stand in the Wu Chi posture.
Work your way from the feet up to the top of the head.
Once you do that, then you go to your breathing.
Inhale, exhale.
OK?
From here, once you have a feeling of peace and focus, that the mind isn't racing around anymore, that you're very calm and relaxed, let's begin the movement then.
Then begin the posture and the movement is what we're going to do, which is gathering chi from heaven and earth.